Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy, Dean's Office; Records ua680
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects, 1965-1986; 5; 4.5 cubic ft.
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Viewpoints, 1966-1968 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 16)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Surveys, 1966 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 17)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Surveys, 1967 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 18)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Surveys, 1968 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 19)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Charters, 1967 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 20)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Annual (blue bound), 1966 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 21)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Annual (blue bound), 1967 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 22)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Annual (blue bound), 1968 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 23)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Annual (blue bound), 1968 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 24)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Annual (blue bound), 1969 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 25)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Surveys of Metropolitan Planning, 1967 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 26)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Surveys of Metropolitan Planning, 1968 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 27)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Local Government Center - Round Lake Association Report, 1968 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 28)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Working Group Report on the Local Government Center, 1968 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 29)
  - Public Executive Project, Meeting Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 30)
  - Public Executive Project, 1971-1974 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 31)
  - Public Executive Project, ca. 1975-1980 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 32)
  - Public Executive Project, 1979-1980 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 33)
  - GSPA/PEP "State of NY Administrative Analyst's Handbook", 1959-1967 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 1)
  - Public Executive Project Workshop "Financial Aspects of Management", 1978 October 29-November 1 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 2)
  - Public Executive Project (PEP) Workshop "The Management of Installing Automated Job Matching Systems", 1978 November 6-10 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 3)
  - Public Executive Project, Workshop "Executive Role & Methods", 1978 December 3-6 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 4)
  - Public Executive Project, Workshop "Program Planning & Budgeting", 1979 January 10-13 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 5)
  - Public Executive Project, Workshop "Supervisory Management of Human Resources on the Campus", 1979 March 4-7 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 6)
  - Public Executive Project, Workshop, "Management of Human Resources", 1979 April 4-6 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 7)
  - Public Executive Project, Workshop "Managing Programs & Activities on the Campus", 1979 April 8-11 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 8)
  - Public Executive Project, Workshop "Managing Automated Job Matching Systems", 1979 May 7-11 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 9)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program Course Descriptions, 1983-1984 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 10)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course II, 1984 May (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 11)
  - Public Service Training Program - Programs in Administration & Supervision - Course III, 1984 May (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 12)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course I, 1984 May (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 13)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course I Instructor's Guide, 1984 May (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 14)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course II, 1984 May (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 15)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course IV, 1984 May (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 16)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Courses I, II, IV, 1984 September (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 17)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course I, 1984 September (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 18)
  - Public Service Training Program, 1984-1985 (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 19)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course I, 1985 April (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 20)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course II, 1985 April (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 21)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course III, 1985 April (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 22)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course I, 1985 April (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 23)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course II, 1985 April (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 24)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course III, 1985 April (Box 10 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 25)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course II, 1985 May (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 1)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course IV, 1985 May (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 2)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course IV, 1985 May (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 3)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration, ca. 1985 (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 4)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course IV, 1985 August (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 5)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course II, 1985 August (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 6)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course III, 1985 August (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 7)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course I, 1985 October (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 8)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course III, 1985 October (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 9)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course I, 1985 October (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 10)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course III, 1985 October (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 11)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course III, 1985 October (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 12)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course IV, 1985 October (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 13)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course I, ca. 1985 (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 14)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration - Course IV, ca. 1985 (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 15)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision - Course IV, ca. 1985 (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 16)
  - Public Service Training Program "Accounting and Financial Decision Making", 1986 August (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 17)
  - Public Service Training Program "Information Management", 1986 August (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 18)
  - Public Service Training Program "Program Planning & Evaluation", ca. 1986 August (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 19)
  - Public Service Training Program - Accounting & Financial Decision Making, 1986 (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 20)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration- Course I, ca. 1986 (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 21)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration- Course II, ca. 1986 (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 22)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration- Course III, ca. 1986 (Box 11 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 23)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration- Course III, ca. 1986 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 1)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Administration- Course IV, ca. 1986 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 2)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision- Course I, ca. 1985 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 3)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision- Course III, ca. 1986 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 4)
  - Public Service Training Program - Program in Supervision- Course IV, ca. 1986 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 5)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Center, 1977-1980 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 6)
  - Center for Governmental Research & Services, 1978-1981 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 7)
  - Center for Study of Public Policy, 1973-1977 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 8)
  - Educational Community Center (ECC), 1978-1980 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 9)
  - Office of Research & Educational Development, 1979 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 10)
  - Public Affairs Study Center, 1971; 1974 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 11)
  - Robert Taft Institute of Government, 1976-1981 (Box 12 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 12)
- GSPA Publications, 1958-1980; 6; 2 Vol.
  This records series contains newsletters from the Albany Graduate Program in Public Administration, 1961-1962. The University Libraries also hold 7 issues of the newsletter (1962-1965). The University Libraries hold issues of several GSPA publications. The University Libraries holds an incomplete run of Rockefeller College Report (1984-1987), a newsletter covering activities of Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy. The University Libraries hold one issue of Contact: Undergraduate Political Science Advisor (1988), a Political Science Department publication, and four issues of the Political Science Newsletter (1973-1974). The University Libraries hold seven issues of The Docket (1982-86), a GPSA produced publication of the International Political Science Association (ISPA) Research Committee on Comparative Judicial Studies. The University Libraries hold seven issues of GSPA Alumni Newsletter (1978-1980, 1983) and three issues of The Public Affair (1976), a publication of the Graduate Student Association of GSPA. The University Libraries hold seven issues of The Helderberg Review (1970-1973), a GSPA published journal featuring graduate student work that began publication in 1970. GSPA Bulletins for 1958-59 through 1978-80 are available in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives. After 1980, school specific bulletins were no longer published, and information can be obtained from the University at Albany Graduate and Undergraduate Bulletins.
  - Albany Graduate Program in Public Administration - Newsletters, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (6-GSPA Publications), Folder 1)
- Faculty Publications, 1961-1986; 7; 1 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically by year of publication
  The Public Affairs Monograph Series Publications were kept together and placed at the beginning of the series. This records series consists of essays, articles, bibliographies, surveys, study guides, resource guides, workshop materials and monographs. Individual and collaborative projects related to GSPA, or one of GSPA's related centers and institutes, are included in the series.
  GSPA faculty authored the vast majority, but not all, of the items in this series. Publications resulting from collaborative projects do include items written by persons outside GSPA. The series includes a collection of case studies created for use as supplemental graduate course materials. This collection was written as a collaborative project with outside authors during 1976-77. The collection consists of the "The Jones Island Case", "Design & Delivery: The Dilemma at Eleanor Roosevelt", "The Sheltered Workshop in Troy", "College for the Disadvantaged", "Adjudication of Moving Traffic Violations in NYC", "Snow Emergency in NYC", and "Solid Waste Management in Synonym City: A Case Study". The record series also includes items from the GSPA Reprint Series, the Public Affairs Monograph Series (six books), and the Legislative Security Monograph Series. Only the seventh monograph of the Legislative Security Monograph Series is present in the GSPA records. The record series includes Dr. Robert Rienow's lecture and study guide to "Man Against His Environment" Television Series, 1969. The videos from the television series are available through the University at Albany Libraries.
  - Public Affairs Monograph Series Publications - Byron Hipple, "Local Public Welfare Administration in NYS...", 1962 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 2)
  - Public Affairs Monograph Series Publications - Byron T. Hipple, "Fiscal Policy and the Public Social Services", 1966 April (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 3)
  - Public Affairs Monograph Series Publications - Fred Tickner, "Training in Modern Society", 1966 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 4)
  - Public Affairs Monograph Series Publications - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "The Massachusetts Town Meeting A Tenacious Institution", 1967 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 5)
  - Public Affairs Monograph Series Publications - Herinan E. Hilleboe & Morris Schaefer, "Papers & Bibliogaphy on Community Health Planning", 1967 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 6)
  - Public Affairs Monograph Series Publications - Richard J. Kalish & Donald J. Reeb, "Economic Welfare and the Development of the Mohawk Region" (3 copies, I copy includes an errata sheet), 1967 (Box 2 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 7)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - "A Bibliography of Comparative Government", 1964; 1967 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 2)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Harold A. Adams, "The Sheltered Workshop in Troy", 1976 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 3)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Harold Adams & Walter Balk, "An Analysis of the Division of Vocational Rehabilitation", 1968 (Box 3 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 4)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Carlos Alberto Astiz, "The Changing Face of Latin American Higher Education", 1967 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 5)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Walter L. Balk et al, editors, "Administering State Government Productivity Improvement Guidelines" Workshop, 1974 September 23-25 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 6)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Walter L. Balk editor, "Motivating State Government Productivity Improvement Programs", Workshop, 1974 November 18-30 (Box 4 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 7)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Bernard H. Budmen, "The Jones Island Case", 1977 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 8)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Raymond Cox "Administrative Questions in Legislative Reform", 1981 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 9)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - "Final Report: Employment Opportunities for the Elderly", ca. 1977 (Box 5 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 10)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Douglas Fisher, "Expectations, the Term Structure of Interest Rates and Recent British Experience", 1966 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 11)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Jack E. Gelfand, "The Credit Elasticity of Lower-Middle Income Housing Demand", 1966 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 12)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - "GSPA Romantic Relations in Organizations: 3rd Party Observer - A Survey", 1975 (Box 6 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 13)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - GSPA Survey "Romantic Relations in Organizations 3d Party Observer's View", 1975 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 14)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - James Heaphey, editor, Legislative Security Monograph #7, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 15)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Byron T Hipple, "The Constitution and the State's Social Services", 1967 (Box 7 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 16)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Alvin Magid, "Dimensions of Administrative Role & Conflict Resolution Among Local Officials in N. Nigeria", 1967 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 17)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Richard 1. Nunez, "Adjudication of Moving Traffic Violations in NYC", 1976 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 18)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Orville F. Poland, "California State Finances", 1966 (Box 8 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 19)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Frank W. Prescott & Joseph F. Zimmerman, "The Council of Revision...", 1973 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 20)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Robert I. Quinn, "Design & Delivery: The Dilemma at Eleanor Roosevelt", 1976 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 21)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Robert E. Quinn & John Rohrbaugh, "A Spatial Model of Effectiveness Criteria...", 1981 (Box 9 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 22)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Donald J. Reeb, "An Inquiry in the Economic Goal Structure of Urban Affairs", 1966 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 23)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - James A. Riedel, "Boss & Faction ", 1964 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 24)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Morris Schaefer, "The Health Manpower Crisis: Cause or Symptom", 1967 (Box 10 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 25)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - James A. Riedel, "Boss & Function ", 1964 GSPA Reprint Series, 1966 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 26)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Dr. Robert Rienow, "Man Against His Environment", Television Series, 1969 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 27)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Robert Rienow, "Man Against His Environment" SUNY Television Series, 1969 (Box 11 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 28)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Rockefeller College Resource Guide for Human Service Professionals on Homelessness Resource Guide Series, ca. 1986 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 29)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - E. S. Savas, "Snow Emergency in NYC", 1976 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 30)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Jay M. Shafritz, "Solid Waste Management in Synonym City: A Case Study", 1976 (Box 12 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 31)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Robert M. Stout, "Working Sources in Public Law," GSPA Working Sources in Public Law, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 32)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Robert Stout, editor, "Local Government In-Service Training", 1968 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 33)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Troy R. Westmeyer & Meg C. Rorer, "College for the Disadvantaged", 1976 (Box 13 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 34)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Theodore P. Wright, Jr., "The Muslim League in South India Since Independence: A Study in Minority Group Political Strategy", 1966 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 35)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Theodore Wright, Jr., "The Dar-us-Salam Case in Hyderbad National Integration & Modern Judicial Procedures", 1966 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 36)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "Chaos or Correction ", 1966 (Box 14 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 37)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "Executive Secretary Plan in Massachusetts", 1967 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 38)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "Metropolitan Ecumenism: The Road to the Promised Land ", 1967 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 39)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "On the Other Hand", 1966 (Box 15 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 40)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "Metropolitan Ecumenism: Return to the Promised Land ", 1967 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 41)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "Pre-Employment Physical Examination ", 1965 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 42)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "Representative Town Meeting", 1966 (Box 16 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 43)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "The Open Town Meeting: A Tenacious Institution", 1965 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 44)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "State Agencies for Local Affairs: The Institutionalization of State Assistance to Local Government", 1968 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 45)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "Town Manager Plan in Massachusetts", 1966 (Box 17 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 46)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "Twentieth Century Selectmen," GSPA Reprint Series (21 items), 1966-1967 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 47)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman, "Whither Town Government", 1966 (Box 1 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 48)
  - GSPA Reprint Series - Joseph F. Zimmerman & Mary E. Snyder, "New Trends in Area Planning", 1967 (Box 18 (7-Faculty Publications), Folder 49)
- Hannah B. Applebaum Files, 1963-1971; 8; 0.5 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject file type, and then chronologically within each subject file type.
  Hannah Applebaum was the GSPA librarian for several years, and this series contains her records. This series consists of the H. Applebaum's files, 1963-1971, and contains course descriptions and reading lists, and a copy of the report of the Search Committee for a Political Science Chairman (1966). The remaining files contain copies of official memos and faculty meeting minutes. The GSPA file contains additional course schedules, memos and copies of The Dean's Report to the Board of Trustees on the First Year (1963), and the Visiting Committee's Report on the Local Government Center (1968).
  - H. Applebaum, 1963-1965 (Box 1 (8-Hannah B. Applebaum Files), Folder 1)